Anthony Drake

Avon, IN | t27duck@gmail.com

GitHub: github.com/t27duck LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/t27duck

Twitter: @t27duck Website: t27duck.com

Over **10 years** of professional experience developing web sites and web applications both in a team environment and working alone. I am a strong believer in doing things right the first time and striving for obtainable **long term goals** rather than short term gains via gut reactions. The thrill of using programming to **solve problems** with creative solutions is what I enjoy most about my career.

Professional Experience

Springbuk

Senior Software Engineer July 2017 – Present

- Introduced react into the main application to promote encapsulation and consistency for page elements
- Implemented anonymization system to allow users access to various areas of the app while protecting sensitive identifying information

MOBI (mobiwm.com)

Senior Web Developer

June 2011 - July 2017

- Helped design and implement custom web reporting framework and related features
- Implemented process of importing and error checking of client employee information and raw mobile carrier data for later use and bill optimization
- Lead major project to upgrade core application to latest Rails and Ruby version
- Mentored developers regarding technical and architectural questions and promoted best practices
- Worked closely with team leads to help promote cross-team collaboration

GoNintendo.com / GoingSony.com Web Developer, Server Admin Oct 2006 – Present

- Migrated disjoined WordPress and phpBB site into a unified, custom built PHP site (July 2011)
- Rebuilt site and migrated from PHP / MySQL to Ruby on Rails / PostgreSQL (May 2015)
- Implemented mobile-friendly custom story authoring and commenting system
- Maintains and updates existing web server running CentOS

Bluefish Wireless, Inc.

Web Developer

April 2008 – June 2011

- Built and maintained fully customized web ordering and reporting client web portals
- Maintain and improved internal CRM and order ticketing system
- Built internal IT change request system

Skills and Expertise

Ruby on Rails React NGINX PHP

PostgreSQLRedisMySQLAdobe ColdFusionjQuery + JavaScriptLinux (CentOS, Arch)GitVisual Basic 6

Education

Indiana University-Purdue University at Indianapolis

2005 - 2009

Bachelor of Science, Computer Information Technology, Web Development